keenswh.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Keen Software House

Please read these Privacy Policy carefully before using this site.  
Date of Last Revision: September, 2014

 **Keen Software House a. s. Privacy Policy**

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At KeenSWH.com, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

KeenSWH.com does not collect any personal information about you when you visit our web site. We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using or the type of operating system you are using.

To enhance your experience with our site, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site, but it is recommended.

 **KeenSWH.com Account Policy  
**  
You may access some of our services by signing up for a KeenSWH.com account and providing us with some personal information. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: username and password (optional data is email address). When you create an account on KeenSWH.com, certain information that you provide (e.g. username) is visible to other users of KeenSWH.com.

Keen Software House a. s. does not rent or sell your personal information with other people or non-affiliated companies except when we have your permission.

 **Electronic Newsletters Policy**

We offer a free electronic newsletter to users. KeenSWH.com gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. KeenSWH.com will never disclose your name or email address to third parties.

 **Surveys**

KeenSWH.com may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

 **Linked Web Sites**

We may provide links to third-party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third-party sites.

 **Questions?**

Contact us - [info@keenswh.com](mailto:info@keenswh.com)
